Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student records and office files, 1968-1987; Accession 1990-A-041
  - Humanities and Social Science
    - Enrollment, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1220)
    - Faculty, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1221)
    - Grades, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1222)
    - Payroll, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1223)
    - Registration, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1224)
    - Applications Rejected, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1225)
    - General, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1226)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1227)
    - Registrar Applications, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1228)
    - Summer Language Institute: Letters to Heads of Instruction, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1229)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1230)
    - Statistics, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1231)
    - Class Lists, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1232)
    - Grades, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1233)
    - Summer Language Institute: Policies and Procedure, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1235)
    - Summer Language Institute: Letters to Heads of Instruction, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1236)
    - Form Letter: "am still waiting for material", 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1237)
    - Grade Lists, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1238)
    - CLass Lists: 8 Week, Summer Language Institute, Humanities and Social Science, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1239)
    - Class Lists: Science, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1240)
    - Class Lists: 5 Week Program, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1241)
    - Dummy Social Security Numbers, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1242)
    - Course Lists, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1243)
    - Sciences: Course Lists, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1244)
    - Summer Language Institute: Policies and Procedures, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1245)
    - Dummy Social Security Numbers, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1246)
    - Class List: Science, First and Second Semester, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1247)
    - Class List: 5 Week, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1248)
    - Class List: 8 Week, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1249)
    - Dummy Social Security Numbers, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1250)
    - Class Lists: 5 week, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1251)
    - Class List Copies: 8 Week, Xerox Copies, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1252)
    - Returned Class Lists, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1253)
    - Reports, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1254)
    - Dummy Social Security Numbers, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1255)
    - Summer Language Institute: Letters to Heads of Instruction, Reports, etc., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1257)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1258)
- Records, 1984-1986; Accession 1990-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - 1985 Summer and Special Programs
    - Originals (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Budget (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Advertising (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Advance Requests (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Expense Reports (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Misc. - Directory, Service, Telephone, etc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Postage (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Printing Service (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Purchasing Requisitions (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Quick Copy (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Service Requests (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Stock Requests (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Telephone (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Transfers (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - SLI, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ELOP, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sciences, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hum. and S.S., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Drama, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Adult Program, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Adult Program - Peabody Museum, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Counselors/Student Activities, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Elderhostel, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Shafer, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Shafer Scholars, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dance Program, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Reserve, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Advisory Committee/Meetings, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - NAASS Meeting, 1985 March 24-26 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Broadsheet, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Calendar, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Chrono. S & SP, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Incoming Correspondence S & SP, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Elderhostel: 1985
    - Open House, 1985 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Schedules, Activities, Courses, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Originals., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Misc., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Chrono., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Housing, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Residents: Week of Jun 16, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Commuters: Week of Jun 16, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Residents: Week of Jun 23, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Commuters: Week of Jun 23, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Jun 23, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Jun 16, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Forms, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Planning, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1986 H.S. Open House, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Film Series, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Programs (other), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Special Programs - Augusta, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - University Information, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Summer Lecture Series Information, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Advertising records, 1985-1987; Accession 1990-A-099
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - Advertising: General Material, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Dance Festival, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Art New England, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aurora Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Boston Globe, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campus Calendar, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cass Communications, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chronicle for Higher Education, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - College Conference Manual, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Woman Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dance Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dramatics Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Greenwich Time Advocate, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hartford Courant, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Inquirer Newspapers, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Live (Music Festival Magazine), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - MBW Advertising Network, Inc., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - New Haven Register, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - New Journal, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - New York Times, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Peterson's Guides (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Reporter, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Scanner, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Daily Texan, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Up Against the Wall, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Vincent Curtis Educational Register, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Westchester and Rockland, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Yale Daily News, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Advertising Material (Temporary), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Education Mailings Clearings House, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Modern Language Association, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Museum Studies, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Sciences, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Special Mailers, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Women's Studies, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Label Master Count, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - College Board, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - The Agency, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Invoices: Tickets, Buses, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - APRO, Inc., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Art New England, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Aurora Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Campus Calendar, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Cass Communications, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Dance, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Dramatics Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - El Mundo, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Hartford Courant, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Harvard Crimson, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Korean-American Journal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Live Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - New Journal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - New Haven Register, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - New York Times, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Peterson's Guides, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - School Guide, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Sherman Foster Johnson Press, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Study in the USA, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Summer on Campus, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Washington Post, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Westchester Rockland Newspapers, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - World Paper, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - WYBC Radio, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Yale Business Bulletin, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Yale Daily News, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Yale Daily News Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Yale Daily News Quarterly, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Yale Dancers Magazine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Yale Herald, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Label Master File, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - American Fund Raising Lists, Inc., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - American Association of Teachers of German (Labels), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - American Passage Media Corp., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Arabic Teachers, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - College Board/Educational Testing Service, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Commercial Mailing Lists, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Greek Orthodox Churches, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Mailing Clearing House, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Metromail Labels, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Modern Language Association, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - New Haven Bus Bills, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Winkle Bus Service Bills, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - American Historical Association (Labels), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - American Passage: CN Operations, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - American Passage (Mailing List), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Art New England, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Boston Globe, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - CEA Advisor, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - College Board Search: Mailing List, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - College Board Testing Information, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Crown and Love Advertising Agency, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Daily Herald, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Dramatics Magazine, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Dramat J. E. and C., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Education Editors' Labels, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Educational Leadership, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Education Week, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - El Mundo, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Graphic Impressions, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Guide to Summer Camps and Schools, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Hartford Courant, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Health Professions Advisors (Mailing List), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Independent Educational Counselors Association, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Journal and Topics Newspapers, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Korean-American Journal, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Mailings Clearing House, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Media House, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Metromail (Mailing List), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Middle East Studies Association, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Modern Language Association, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - National Association of College Administrators and Counselors, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - New Haven Register, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - New Journal, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - New York Times, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - New Yorker, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Peterson's Guides, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Physicians' Camps and Schools Mart, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - School Guide, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - The Star: Ledger, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Study in the USA, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Washington Post, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - World Paper, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - The Writer, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Yale Alumni Records (Labels), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Yale Daily News, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Yale Economic and Business Review, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Yale Herald, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Yale Quarterly, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Yale Public Relations (Labels), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Yale Vernacular, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Zirkus Literary Magazine, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Label Master File, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 166)
- Records, 1987-1989; Accession 1991-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Student Files: 1987 Summer Sessions
  - Yale Summer and Special Programs Office Files
    - Handbooks and Flyers, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1175)
    - Originals, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1176)
    - Duplicates, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1177)
    - Ads, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1178)
    - Advertising, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1179)
    - Advance Requests, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1180)
    - Advertising, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1181)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1182)
    - Expense Reports, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1183)
    - Equipment (Office), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1185)
    - Misc.--Directory, Service, Tele., etc., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1186)
    - IBM PC XT, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1187)
    - Personnel, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1188)
    - Printing Service, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1189)
    - Postage, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1190)
    - Purchasing Requisitions, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1191)
    - Quick Copy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1192)
    - Service Requests, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1193)
    - Stock Requests, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1194)
    - Transfers, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1195)
    - 645A-31-87089 Summer Language Institute, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1196)
    - 645B-31-87089 English Language and Orientation Program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1197)
    - 645C-31-87089 Sciences, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1198)
    - Science Transfers, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1199)
    - 645D-31-87089 Hum and SS, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1200)
    - 645E-31-87089 Handbook, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1201)
    - 645F-31-87089 Drama, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1202)
    - 645G-31-87089 Adult Program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1203)
    - 645H-31-87089 Counselors/Student Activities, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1204)
    - Counselors' List, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1205)
    - 645J-31-87089 Elderhostel, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1206)
    - 645K-31-87089 Shafer, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1207)
    - 645M-31-87089 Dance, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1208)
    - 645X-31-87730 Reserve, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1209)
    - Advisory Committee/Meetings, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1210)
    - NAASS Mtg., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1211)
    - Broadsheet, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1212)
    - Calendar, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1213)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1214)
    - Chrono, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1215)
    - Forms, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1216)
    - Handbook, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1217)
    - Handbook Job Search, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1218)
    - University Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1219)
    - Planning, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1220)
    - Film Series, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1221)
    - Programs (Other), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1222)
  - American Economics Association, 1982
  - American Economic Association, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Cards (Box 6, Folder 1253)
    - Grades (Box 6, Folder 1254)
  - American Economic Association, 1980
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1985-1986
    - Originals (Box 7, Folder 1315)
    - Membrane (Box 7, Folder 1316)
    - Politics (Box 7, Folder 1317)
    - Women (Box 7, Folder 1318)
    - Conferences (Box 7, Folder 1319)
    - Expense Reports (Box 7, Folder 1320)
    - Postage/Purchase/Stock (Box 7, Folder 1321)
    - Printing Service/Quick Copy (Box 7, Folder 1322)
    - Service Requests (Box 7, Folder 1323)
    - Transfers (Box 7, Folder 1324)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 7, Folder 1325)
    - Visiting Faculty Program (Box 7, Folder 1326)
    - Correspondence--Fellows (Box 7, Folder 1327)
    - Correspondence--General (Box 7, Folder 1328)
    - Correspondence--Yale (Box 7, Folder 1329)
    - Chrono (Box 7, Folder 1330)
    - Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 1331)
    - Lecture Series (Box 7, Folder 1332)
    - One-Day Seminars (Box 7, Folder 1333)
    - Personnel (Box 7, Folder 1334)
    - Reciprocal Visits (Box 7, Folder 1349)
    - Registration Forms (Box 7, Folder 1350)
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1984-1985
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1987
    - Originals (Box 8, Folder 1371)
    - Duplicates (Box 8, Folder 1372)
    - Budget (Box 8, Folder 1373)
    - Budget (Box 8, Folder 1374)
    - Expense Reports (Box 8, Folder 1375)
    - Postage/Purchase/Stock Requests (Box 8, Folder 1376)
    - Printing/Quick Copy (Box 8, Folder 1377)
    - Service Requests (Box 8, Folder 1378)
    - Transfers (Box 8, Folder 1379)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 8, Folder 1380)
    - Application Info./Materials (Box 8, Folder 1381)
    - Chrono (Box 8, Folder 1382)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1383)
    - Evaluations (Box 8, Folder 1384)
    - Conferences (Box 8, Folder 1385)
    - One-Day Seminars (Box 8, Folder 1386)
    - Receptions/Luncheons/Meetings (Box 8, Folder 1392)
    - Reciprocal Visits (Box 8, Folder 1393)
    - Registration Forms (Box 8, Folder 1394)
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1987-1988
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1986
    - Originals (Box 8, Folder 1428)
    - Duplicates (Box 8, Folder 1429)
    - Expense Reports (Box 8, Folder 1430)
    - Payroll (Box 8, Folder 1431)
    - Postage/Purchase/Stock Request (Box 8, Folder 1432)
    - Printing/Quick Copy (Box 8, Folder 1433)
    - Service Requests (Box 8, Folder 1434)
    - Transfers (Box 8, Folder 1435)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 8, Folder 1436)
    - Application Information/Materials (Box 8, Folder 1437)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1438)
    - Chrono (Box 8, Folder 1439)
    - Visiting Faculty Program Packet (Box 8, Folder 1440)
    - Evaluations (Box 8, Folder 1441)
    - Visting Faculty Program (Box 8, Folder 1442)
    - Conferences (Box 8, Folder 1443)
    - Lectures (Box 8, Folder 1444)
    - Seminars (Box 8, Folder 1445)
    - American School Reform Movement (Box 8, Folder 1446)
    - Cinematic Literacy: Teaching Orson Welles's "Touch of Evil" (Box 8, Folder 1447)
    - Germans and Jews in Literature Since Lessing (Box 8, Folder 1448)
    - Receptions/Luncheons/Meetings (Box 8, Folder 1449)
    - Reciprocal Visits (Box 8, Folder 1450)
    - Registration Forms (Box 8, Folder 1451)
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1986-1987
  - Summer and Special Programs, 1987
    - Originals (Box 10, Folder 1495)
    - Budget (Box 10, Folder 1496)
    - Advertising (Box 10, Folder 1497)
    - Miscellaneous--Directory, Tele., Water (Box 10, Folder 1498)
    - Expense Reports (Box 10, Folder 1499)
    - Office Equipment (Box 10, Folder 1501)
    - Personnel (Box 10, Folder 1502)
    - Postage (Box 10, Folder 1503)
    - Printing Service (Box 10, Folder 1504)
    - Purchase Requisitions (Box 10, Folder 1505)
    - Quick Copy (Box 10, Folder 1506)
    - Service Requests (Box 10, Folder 1507)
    - Stock Requests (Box 10, Folder 1508)
    - Transfers (Box 10, Folder 1509)
    - 645A-31-87521 SLI (Box 10, Folder 1510)
    - 645B-31-87521 ELOP (Box 10, Folder 1511)
    - 645C-31-87521 Sciences (Box 10, Folder 1512)
    - 645D-31-87521 Hum and SS (Box 10, Folder 1513)
    - 645E-31-87521 Handbook (Box 10, Folder 1514)
    - 645F-31-87521 Drama (Box 10, Folder 1515)
    - 645H-31 Counselors / Student Activities (Box 10, Folder 1516)
    - 645J-31-87521 Elderhostel (Box 10, Folder 1517)
    - 645K-31-87521 Shafer (Box 10, Folder 1518)
    - 645M Grad. and Prof. (Box 10, Folder 1519)
    - 645X-31-87730 Reserve (Box 10, Folder 1520)
    - Advisory Committee Meetings (Box 10, Folder 1521)
    - Broadsheet (Box 10, Folder 1522)
    - Calendar (Box 10, Folder 1523)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 1524)
    - Chrono (Box 10, Folder 1525)
    - Forms (Box 10, Folder 1526)
    - Lectures (Box 10, Folder 1527)
    - Other Programs (Box 10, Folder 1528)
    - University Information (Box 10, Folder 1529)
    - NEH Grants (Box 10, Folder 1530)
    - NEH Proposals for 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1531)
    - NEH Originals (Box 10, Folder 1532)
    - H. Turner Information (Box 10, Folder 1533)
    - NEH Expenses (Box 10, Folder 1534)
    - NEH Transfers (Box 10, Folder 1536)
    - NEH Payroll (Box 10, Folder 1537)
    - NEH Stipends / Salaries (Box 10, Folder 1538)
    - NEH Correspondence / Chrono (Box 10, Folder 1539)
    - NEH Acceptance Packet (Box 10, Folder 1540)
    - NEH Turner Correspondence Information (Box 10, Folder 1542)
- English Language Orientation Program and Summer Program reports, 1963-1985; Accession 1991-A-083
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - English Language Orientation Program and Summer Program reports, 1963-1985 (Box 1)
- Records, 1988-1990; Accession 1992-A-028 (Box 1–7)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Records of the English Language Institute, 1989-1996; Accession 2001-A-093
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Spring - Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spring 1987 - 1988 Eli (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Profiles - Appointment letters 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Spring 1987 - Fall 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fall 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Spring 1990 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fall 1993 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fall 1996 - Course information (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Applications - Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fall 1994 Applications (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Spring 1994 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Spring 1993 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Spring 1991 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Spring 1995 - Eli (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Applications - Fall 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 9 Pamphlets (loose) (Box 1)
- Administrative records, 1978-1983; Accession 2002-A-124
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - Joint ventures with AYA, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Summer Athletic Programs, 1979-1981 (Box 1)
  - Audio/Visual - Language Lab (Box 1)
  - YSP Conferences, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Course of Study Committee, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Special Students Degree Program Proposal (Box 1)
  - Chemical Engineering - Minority, 1981 (Box 1)
  - YSP - Dining Halls, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
  - Evaluation - MandP Staff (Box 1)
  - Summer Faculty, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Film Committee (Box 1)
  - Grades, 1981 (Box 1)
  - "Italians in America, 1701-1891" Colloquium (Box 1)
  - YSP Linguistics Institute, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Scholarships - Summer Programs, 1981 (Box 1)
  - YSP - Housing, 1981-1985 (Box 1)
  - Humanities - Social Sciences Course Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin/Catalogue, 1982 (Box 1)
  - SSP Calendar, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Conference, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Courses, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Drama School Pre-college Program Brochure, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Faculty, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Forestry School "modules", 1982 (Box 1)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Humanities and Social Science courses, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Planning, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Summer School of Music and Art - Norfolk, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Questionnaire, 1982 (Box 1)
  - SSP Scholarships, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Summer Sciences (Box 1)
  - Tuitions (Box 1)
  - YSP - U.S. Grant Foundation (Box 1)
  - World Educational Student Travel group (Box 1)
  - Annual Report and Five-year report 1979-1983 (Box 1)
  - Brochure/catalogue, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Budget (Misc), 1983 (Box 1)
  - Conferences, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Course Descriptions, 1983 (Box 1)
  - ELOP, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Grades, 1983 (Box 1)
  - YSP - Masters (Box 1)
  - Planning - Academic Programs, 1983 (Box 1)
  - SSP Scholarships, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Summer Language Institute (SLI), 1983 (Box 1)
  - Tuskegee Honors Program Instructors, 1983 (Box 1)
  - SLI, 1983 (Box 1)
  - SLI, 1982 (Box 1)
  - 1092 Budget SSP (Box 1)
  - Audit SSP, 1981 (Box 1)
  - YSSP Budget, 1981 (Box 1)
- Administrative records, 1980-1995; Accession 2003-A-060
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - 1984-1985
    - YSP Advertising, Direct Mail etc. (Box 1)
    - 1985 Annual Report (Box 1)
    - 1985 Brochure (Box 1)
    - 1985 Budget (Box 1)
    - YSP Conferences 1985 (Box 1)
    - Computer Center (Box 1)